(Leonard:)How am I the bad guy?
(Leonard:)She's the one who married
someone else. I'm the victim.
(Howard:)Sounds like Zack's the victim.
You're sleeping with his wife.
(Mike:)I've kept my marriage
together for 35 years.
(Mike:)Can I weigh in here?
(Amy:)Sure.
(Mike:)I'm trying to watch the game.
Shut up.
(Mike:)How do you not make
a first down there?
(Sheldon:)They passed against
a nickel defense.
(Sheldon:)They should have run it off-tackle.
(Mike:)How the hell
do you know that?
(Sheldon:)My father loved football.
(Sheldon:)He always made me watch it
(Sheldon:)before I was allowed
to do my homework.
(Howard:)Well...
(Penny:)You'll be happy to know
I just spoke to Zack
(Penny:)and he's willing to
sign the court papers.
(Penny:)He's on his way here now.
(Leonard:)-Wait, you invited him here?
-Yeah.
(Mike:)I'm getting ready
to weigh in again.
(Howard:)Come on.
(Penny:)What do you think
they ought to do now?
(Sheldon:)I would throw a quick slant
to a wide-out,
given that the defense
is showing blitz.